I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Projects Completed/Inactive, 1959-2013 (Box 136-377)
  - Paris, France (Box 349)
    - Le Grand Louvre (Box 349)
      - Name files (Box 354)
        - Lebrat, Jean, 1984-1996 (Box 354)
        - Ligen, Yves, 1989 (Box 354)
        - Macary, Michel, 1984 (Box 354)
        - Mitterand, François, 1982-1987 (Box 354)
        - Nicolet, Roger, 1984 (Box 354)
      - Openings (Box 354)
        - 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 354)
        - 1993, (2 folders) (Box 355)
      - Opinion poll, 1986 (Box 355)
      - Plans and drawings (Box 355)
        - Café Marly in Sully Pavilion, 1990-1991 (Box 355)
        - General, 1984-1989 (Box 355)
        - Plan historique, undated (Box 355)
        - Pyramide Inversée and Hall Carrousel, 1988-1991 (Box 355)
        - Richelieu Wing, 1988 (Box 355)
        - Rohan painting galleries, 1997-1998, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 355, Box 356)
        - Salle Rubens in Richelieu Wing, 1989-1990 (Box 356)
        - Surface Carrousel Tuileries, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 356)
        - Tuileries, 1988, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 356, Box 357)
      - Postcards, 1988 (Box 357)
      - Presentation material, 1984 (Box 357)
      - Publicity (Box 357)
        - 1983-1991 (Box 357)
        - 1993, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 357, Box 358)
      - Reports, 1985, 1991 (Box 358)
      - Rohan painting galleries, 1997-2001, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 358, Box 359)
      - Specifications, 1986-1995, (2 folders) (Box 359)
      - Twentieth anniversary of the pyramid, 2008-2009 See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_016 (Box 359)
      - Visitors, 1988-1990 (Box 359)
    - Tête de la Défense (Box 359)
      - Études techniques et économiques, 1970-1971, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 359, Box 360)
      - General, 1970-1973 See also Containers OV 28-OV 29, Tête de la Défense, (2 folders) (Box 360)
  - Philadelphia, Pa., Society Hill (Box 360)
    - 1959-1965, (3 folders) (Box 360)
    - 1993-1995, 2002-2012 (Box 361)
  - Pittsburgh, Pa., Washington Plaza Apartments, 1960-1963 (Box 361)
  - Princeton, N.J., Laura Spelman Rockefeller Halls, Princeton University, 1969-1974 (Box 361)
  - Purchase, N.Y., MasterCard International Global Headquarters (formerly International Business Machines Corp. Corporate Office Building), 1984-1996, 2007 (Box 361)
  - Rochester, N.Y., Wilson Commons, University of Rochester, 1967-1976 (Box 361)
  - Sacramento, Calif., Sacramento redevelopment, 1960 (Box 361)
  - Sarasota, Fla., New College of Florida dormintories, student union, and academic center, 1961-1965, 2002-2012, (3 folders) (Box 361)
  - Shiga, Japan (Box 361)
    - Miho Institute of Aesthetics chapel (Box 361)
      - General, 2006-2012 (Box 361)
      - Team files - Demirtas, Aslihan, 2006-2009 See also Container OV 25, Miho Institute of Aesthetics chapel, (5 folders) (Box 362)
    - Miho Museum (Box 362)
      - General (Box 362)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 362)
        - 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box 363)
        - 1993, (1 folder) (Box 363, Box 364)
        - 1994-1996 See also Container 6, Certificate of recognition, (6 folders) (Box 364)
        - 1997-2011, (4 folders) (Box 365)
      - Topical files, 1994-1999 See also Container OV 6, Spiral-bound set of presentation drawings, (2 folders) (Box 365, Box 366)
    - Shinji Shumeikai Bell Tower (Box 366)
      - General, 1987-1994, (5 folders) (Box 366)
      - Proposals and fees, 1988-1991 (Box 366)
  - Singapore (Box 367)
    - Gateway Towers (Box 367)
      - General, 1981-2001, (6 folders) (Box 367)
      - Singapore Land Ltd., 1980-1981 (Box 367)
    - Nathan Rd. Development Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 367)
    - Oversea-Chinese Banking Corp. Centre (Box 367)
      - General (Box 367)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 367)
        - 1972-1978, (3 folders) (Box 368)
      - Plaza, 1981-1986, (3 folders) (Box 368)
    - Oversea-Chinese Banking Corp. Centre East, 1987-2001 (Box 368)
    - Raffles City (Box 368)
      - 1970 (Box 368)
      - 1975, (1 folder) (Box 368, Box 369)
      - 1976-1985, (8 folders) (Box 369)
      - 1986-1995, 2005, (3 folders) (Box 370)
    - Raffles Place master plan, 1974-1975 (Box 370)
    - Robinson Towers, 1996-1997 (Box 370)
    - Singapore International Exhibition and Convention Centre, 1962, 1975-1976, 1988-1989 (Box 370)
  - Somers, N.Y., International Business Machines Corp. office building complex, 1983-1986, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 370)
  - Stamford, Conn., Pitney Bowes World Headquarters, 1980-1982 (Box 370)
  - Suzhou Shi, China (Box 371)
    - City Planning project, 1988-1998 See also Containers OV 7, OV 8, OV 26, OV 37, and OV 38, Suzhou Shi, China, (3 folders) (Box 371)
    - Suzhou Museum (Box 371)
      - General, 2000-2011, (4 folders) (Box 371)
      - Topical files, 2005-2008, (2 folders) (Box 372)
  - Sydney, Australia, Australia Square, 1960-1961 (Box 372)
  - Syracuse, N.Y. (Box 372)
    - Everson Museum of Art (Box 372)
      - General, 1961-1969, 1982, 1993-2008, (2 folders) (Box 372)
      - Restoration and renovation (Box 372)
        - 2000, (3 folders) (Box 372)
        - 2001-2002, (3 folders) (Box 373)
    - S. I. Newhouse Communications Center, Syracuse University, 1961-1965, 1975 (Box 373)
  - T'ai-chung shih, Taiwan, Luce Memorial Chapel (Box 373)
    - General, 1957-1966, 1986, 1995-2006, (3 folders) (Box 373)
    - Photographs, 1961-1964 (Box 373)
  - Taipei, Taiwan, Tan Shui residential project, 1995 (Box 374)
  - Tallahassee, Fla., hotel project, 1987 (Box 374)
  - Toronto, Canada, Commerce Court, Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce (Box 374)
    - General, 1968-1978, 1998 (Box 374)
    - Photographs, 1968-1978, 1998 (Box 374)
  - Wallingford, Conn. (Box 374)
    - Choat Rosemary Hall Science Center, 1985-1994 (Box 374)
    - Paul Mellon Center for the Arts, Choate Rosemary Hall, 1967-1977, 1997 (Box 374)
  - Washington, D.C. (Box 374)
    - Columbia Square, 1983-1985 (Box 374)
    - East Building of the National Gallery of Art (Box 374)
      - Congratulations, 1977-1981, (2 folders) (Box 374)
      - General See also Container OV 39, Washington, D.C. (Box 374)
        - 1967-1991, (2 folders) (Box 374)
        - 1992-2013, (2 folders) (Box 375)
    - Embassy of the People's Republic of China, 2000-2010 (Box 375)
    - Slayton, William, residence, 1964, 2003-2008 (Box 375)
    - Southwest Washington urban renewal plan, 1960-1964, 1999-2000 (Box 375)
    - Third Church of Christ, Scientist and Christian Science Monitor, 2006-2008 (Box 375)
  - Wilmington, Del., Wilmington Tower, 1968-1973, 1999-2004 (Box 375)
  - Wiltshire, England, Oare Pavilion (Box 375)
    - Chin, Perry, files See also Container OV 40, Plans and drawings (Box 375)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2003, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 375, Box 376)
      - Topical files, 1999-2003 (Box 376)
    - Client correspondence, 1999-2000 See also Container OV 8, Spiral-bound set of presentation drawings (Box 376)
    - General, 2000-2010, (3 folders) (Box 376)
    - Topical files, 1999-2005, (4 folders) (Box 377)
- Projects Aborted, 1966-2011 (Box 377-388)
  Correspondence, memoranda, photographs, meeting minutes, proposals, contracts, financial documents, clippings, studies, reports, blueprints, architectural renderings, plans, drawings, maps mostly relating to projects that were initiated by Pei or his firm, but never completed. The only exception to this is the China Pavilion at Expo ’70 that was completed, but for which Pei was the supervising architect. Pei's staff designated these projects as "aborted."
  - Athens, Greece, Athens Museum of Contemporary Art (Box 377)
    - General See also Container OV 16, Athens, Greece (Box 377)
      - 1980-1981, 1992-1993, (4 folders) (Box 377)
      - 1994-2011, (8 folders) (Box 378)
    - Team files, 2000-2001, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 378, Box 379)
    - Topical files, 1995-2002, (3 folders) (Box 379)
  - Augusta, Ga., Broad Street revitalization (Box 379)
    - Coliseum, 1973-1977 (Box 379)
    - Downtown development, 1974-1976 (Box 379)
    - Holley, Eugene, 1973-1976 (Box 379)
  - Bankgkok, Thailand, U.S. Embassy, 1987-1989 (Box 379)
  - Beijing, China (Box 380)
    - U.S. Embassy Compound, 1979-1987 (Box 380)
    - U.S. Exhibition Center, 1979-1987, (5 folders) (Box 380)
  - Bilbao, Spain, Bilbao Emblematic Building (Box 380)
    - Binder, 1991 (Box 380)
    - General (Box 380)
      - 1990 (Box 380)
      - 1991-1996 See also Containers OV 9-OV 10, Bilbao, Spain, (2 folders) (Box 381)
  - Buenos Aires, Argentina, Austral Lineas Aereas, 1979-1982 (Box 381)
  - Cairo, Egypt, Cairo Museum, 1979-1982 (Box 381)
  - Columbus, Ohio, Galbreath project, 1980 (Box 381)
  - Costa Mesa, Calif., Segerstrom Properties, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 381)
  - Dallas, Tex., Carrozza project, 1977 (Box 381)
  - Hong Kong, Shanghai Commercial Bank, 1998-2000 (Box 381)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia, Bank Dagang Nasional Indonesia Center (Box 382)
    - Art collection, 1994-1998 (Box 382)
    - General (Box 382)
      - 1991-1996, (6 folders) (Box 382)
      - 1997-2004 (Box 383)
  - La Rochefoucauld, France, Château de La Rochefoucauld (Box 383)
    - Contract, 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box 383)
    - General, 1993-2004 See also Container OV 10, La Rochefoucauld, France, (3 folders) (Box 383)
  - London, England, Asia House (Box 383)
    - Contract, 2000 (Box 383)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 383)
    - Drawings, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 384)
    - Rand, Chris, file, 1999 See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_014 (Box 384)
  - Mexico City, Mexico, Corporate Office Building, 1980-1983 (Box 384)
  - New York, N.Y. (Box 384)
    - Museum of American Folk Art, 1986 (Box 384)
    - U.S. Custom House (Box 384)
      - General, 1973-1974 (Box 384)
      - Planning study, 1974, (2 folders) (Box 384)
    - Vivian Beamont Theater (Box 384)
      - 1981 (Box 384)
      - 1982 (Box 385)
  - Osaka, Japan, China Pavilion at Expo '70 (Box 385)
    - Catalogs and publications, 1966-1970, (2 folders) (Box 385)
    - General See also Container OV 26, Two bound sets of blueprints (Box 385)
      - 1968-1970, (5 folders) (Box 385)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 386)
    - Photographs, 1970 (Box 386)
    - Topical files, 1968-1974 See also Container OV 41, Drawings (Box 386)
  - Paris, France (Box 386)
    - Hôtel d'Iéna, 1991-1993 (Box 386)
    - Place du Palais Royal (Box 386)
      - General, 1993-1997 (Box 386)
      - Project summary, 1996 (Box 386)
  - San Antonio, Tex., Gill Savings, 1981-1982 (Box 386)
  - San Francisco, Calif. (Box 386)
    - Ferry Building, 1980-1983 See also Container OV 16, San Francisco (Box 386)
    - Mission Bay, 1982-1985 (Box 387)
  - Singapore, Chung Khiaw Bank, 1968-1974, (2 folders) (Box 387)
  - Tehran, Iran (Box 387)
    - Industrial Credit Bank, 1976-1979 (Box 387)
    - Kapsad Development, 1974-1977, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 387, Box 388)
  - Williamsburg, Va., Peacock Hill, 1980-1981 (Box 388)
- Projects Proposed, 1952-2012 (Box 388-413)
  Correspondence, memoranda, project proposals and reports, meeting minutes, plans, maps, lists, report forms, photographs, financial records, newspaper clippings, and other printed matter documenting projects either declined by Pei or accepted by him but later cancelled, as well as projects for which Pei’s firm was not selected by the client. Pei’s staff created the series and characterized the projects filed within it as “proposed.” Documentation for most projects is not extensive since many of the projects did not progress much beyond the initial inquiry from a prospective client or preliminary fact gathering by Pei’s staff. In addition to individual project files, report forms provide single-sheet summaries of prospective projects for the 1960s and 1970s.
  Arranged chronologically by year or year span and alphabetically therein by name of city or country. A list of files dated 1952-1991 is located at the beginning of the series and records project names.
  - List of files (1952-1991), undated (Box 388)
  - 1952 (Box 388)
    - Caracas, Venezuela (Box 388)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Box 388)
  - 1954, miscellaneous (Box 388)
  - 1959 (Box 388)
    - Aspen, Colo.; Baychester, Bronx, N.Y.; Chicago, Ill.; Hangzhou, China (Box 388)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii; Louisville, Ky.; Montevideo, Uruguay (Box 388)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 388)
    - Rochester, N.Y.; Toronto, Canada; Utica, N.Y. (Box 388)
  - 1960, Bloomfield, Conn.; Honolulu, Hawaii; Minneapolis, Minn.; New York, N.Y.; San Francisco, Calif.; Vancouver, Canada (Box 388)
  - 1960-1961, New York, N.Y., Central City General Post Office (Box 388)
  - circa 1961-1969, report forms on prospective jobs, A-Z, (3 folders) (Box 389)
  - 1961 (Box 389)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 389)
    - Boston, Mass.; Brooklyn, N.Y.; Dallas, Tex. (Box 389)
    - Grand Rapids, Mich.; Guinea; High Point, N.C.; Indianapolis, Ind.; Islamabad, Pakistan (Box 389)
    - Louisville, Ky.; Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 389)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 389)
    - Oakland, Calif.; Palm Beach, Fla. (Box 389)
    - Paris, France; Piffard, N.Y. (Box 389)
    - Providence, R.I.; Queens, N.Y. (Box 389)
    - Regina, Canada; Salt Lake City, Utah; Taipei, Taiwan (Box 390)
    - Toronto, Canada; Washington, D.C.; Wichita, Kansas (Box 390)
  - 1962 (Box 390)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 390)
    - Brooklyn, N.Y.; Columbus, Ohio; Dallas, Tex.; Edmonton, Canada; Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 390)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 390)
    - Ottawa, Canada; Pittsburgh, Pa.; Providence, R.I.; St. Louis, Mo.; San Antonio, Tex. (Box 390)
    - Staten Island, N.Y. (Box 390)
    - Toronto, Canada; Vancouver, Canada; Washington, D.C. (Box 390)
  - 1963 (Box 390)
    - Boston, Mass.; Charlotte Amalie, V.I.; Chicago, Ill.; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 390)
    - Los Angeles, Calif.; Mexico City, Mexico; Newport, R.I. (Box 390)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 390)
    - Oberlin, Ohio; Palm Beach, Fla.; Phoenix, Ariz.; Providence, R.I.; Short Hills, N.J.; Springfield, Mass.; Tacoma, Wash. (Box 390)
    - Tel-Aviv, Israel; Toledo, Ohio; Troy, N.Y.; University City, Mo.; Worcester, Mass.; Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio (Box 390)
  - 1964 (Box 390)
    - Boston, Mass.; Lahore, Pakistan (Box 390)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 390)
    - Rochester, N.Y.; Storrs, Conn. (Box 390)
  - 1965, Dallas, Tex.; Eleuthera Island, Bahamas; Honolulu, Hawaii; Providence, R.I. (Box 391)
  - 1966-1970, Washington, D.C. (Box 391)
  - 1967, New York, N.Y. (Box 391)
  - 1968 (Box 391)
    - Brooklyn, N.Y.; New York, N.Y. (Box 391)
    - New York, N.Y., International Business Machines Corp. (IBM) headquarters (Box 391)
    - New York, N.Y.; Springfield, Ill. (Box 391)
    - Taipei, Taiwan (Box 391)
  - 1969, Miami, Fla.; Minneapolis, Minn.; New York, N.Y. (Box 391)
  - 1970-1979, report forms on prospective jobs, (2 folders) (Box 391)
  - 1970, miscellaneous (Box 391)
  - 1971 (Box 391)
    - Dallas, Tex.; Des Moines, Iowa (Box 392)
    - Montreal, Canada; New Orleans, La.; New York, N.Y. (Box 392)
    - Paris, France; San Antonio, Tex.; Singapore; Washington, D.C. (Box 392)
  - 1972 (Box 392)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 392)
    - Columbus, Ohio; Greenvale, N.Y. (Box 392)
    - Lille, France (Box 392)
    - Macomb, Ill.; Montreal, Canada (Box 392)
    - New York, N.Y.; Oberlin, Ohio; Puerto Rico (Box 392)
    - Queens, N.Y.; Seattle, Wash.; Washington, D.C. (Box 392)
  - 1973 (Box 392)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 392)
    - Atlanta, Ga.; Berea, Ky.; Boston, Mass.; Columbia, S.C.; Dearborn, Mich.; Detroit, Mich.; Europe; Guatemala City, Guatemala (Box 393)
    - Los Angeles, Calif.; Miami, Fla. (Box 393)
    - New Haven, Conn. (Box 393)
    - New York, N.Y., (3 folders) (Box 393)
    - Paris, France, Jean Dubuffet project (Box 393)
      - Correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 393)
      - Drawings and plans See also Container OV 10, 1973, Paris, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 393, Box 394)
      - Expenses (Box 394)
    - Richmond, Va.; Rochester, N.Y.; Saudi Arabia (Box 394)
    - Taipei, Taiwan; Toledo, Ohio; Washington, D.C. (Box 394)
  - 1974 (Box 394)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 394)
    - Athens, Ga.; Atlanta, Ga.; Beaumont, Tex.; Brooklyn, N.Y.; Cleveland, Ohio; Detroit, Mich. (Box 394)
    - Haifa, Israel; Houston, Tex.; Indianapolis, Ind.; Madrid, Spain (Box 394)
    - Miami, Fla.; New Rochelle, N.Y. (Box 394)
    - New York, N.Y.; Paris, France; Racine, Wisc. (Box 394)
    - Raleigh, N.C.; St.-Jean-Cap-Ferrat, France; San Francisco, Calif.; Saudi Arabia (Box 394)
    - Staten Island, N.Y.; Torino, Italy; Wichita, Kans.; Wilmington, N.C. (Box 394)
  - 1975 (Box 394)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 394)
    - Atlanta, Ga.; Charleston, S.C.; Columbia, S.C.; Dublin, Ireland (Box 394)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii; Kuwait; Manila, Philippines (Box 395)
    - Milwaukee, Wisc. (Box 395)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 395)
    - Peoria, Ill.; Richmond, Va. (Box 395)
    - Saudi Arabia; Singapore (Box 395)
    - Staten Island, N.Y.; Tehran, Iran (Box 395)
  - 1976 (Box 395)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 395)
    - Adelaide, Australia; Boston, Mass.; Cairo, Egypt (Box 395)
    - Dawhah, Qatar, (2 folders) (Box 395)
    - Fort Lauderdale, Fla.; Indianapolis, Ind.; Kuwait; Manila, Philippines (Box 396)
    - Miami, Fla. (Box 396)
    - Montreal, Canada (Box 396)
    - New York, N.Y.; Newark, N.J. (Box 396)
    - Oklahoma, Okla.; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Springfield, Ohio; Syracuse, N.Y.; Washington, D.C. (Box 396)
  - 1977 (Box 396)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 396)
    - Boston, Mass.; Brooklyn, N.Y.; Cairo, Egypt (Box 396)
    - Cherry Hill, N.J.; Dallas, Tex.; Dhahran, Saudi Arabia (Box 396)
    - Hong Kong (Box 397)
    - Jakarta, Indonesia; Kent, N.Y. (Box 397)
    - Lagos, Nigeria; London, England (Box 397)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 397)
    - Phoenix, Ariz.; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Taipei, Taiwan; Yemen (Box 397)
  - 1978 (Box 397)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 397)
    - Boston, Mass.; London, England (Box 397)
    - New Brunswick, N.J.; Richmond, Va.; Singapore (Box 398)
    - West Palm Beach, Fla., (2 folders) (Box 398)
  - 1979 (Box 398)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 398)
    - Abilene, Tex. (Box 398)
    - Cambridge, Mass.; Hong Kong; Houston, Tex. (Box 398)
    - Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 398)
    - New York, N.Y.; United Arab Emirates (Box 398)
  - 1980 (Box 399)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 399)
    - Athens, Greece (Box 399)
    - Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 399)
    - Caracas, Venezuela; Charlottesville, Va. (Box 399)
    - Columbia, S.C., (2 folders) (Box 399)
    - Dallas, Tex.; Hong Kong (Box 399)
    - Jerusalem, Israel; Miami, Fla.; Portland, Oreg. (Box 399)
    - San Francisco, Calif.; Singapore (Box 399)
  - 1981 (Box 399)
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 399, Box 400)
    - Billancourt, France; Boston, Mass.; Greenwich, Conn.; Kuwait; London, England (Box 400)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 400)
      - East River development, (2 folders) (Box 400)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 400)
    - Paris, France; Queensland, Australia; Rome, Italy (Box 400)
    - Sakkara, Egypt; San Antonio, Tex.; Singapore; Washington, D.C. (Box 400)
    - West Palm Beach, Fla., (1 folder) (Box 400, Box 401)
  - 1982 (Box 401)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 401)
    - Cambridge, Mass.; Chicago, Ill.; Dallas, Tex. (Box 401)
  - 1983 (Box 401)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 401)
    - Boston, Mass.; Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia (Box 401)
    - Miami, Fla.; Minneapolis, Minn.; New York, N.Y. (Box 401)
    - Paris, France; Singapore (Box 401)
    - Venice, Italy, (1 folder) (Box 401, Box 402)
  - 1984 (Box 402)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 402)
    - Chicago, Ill.; Lexington, Ky. (Box 402)
    - Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 402)
    - Phoenix, Ariz.; Singapore (Box 402)
  - 1985 (Box 402)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 402)
    - Atlanta, Ga.; London, England; Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 402)
    - New York, N.Y.; Shanghai, China (Box 402)
  - 1986 (Box 402)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 402)
      - A-K (Box 402)
      - L-Z (Box 403)
    - Asheville, N.C.; Atlanta, Ga.; Heathrow, Fla. (Box 403)
    - London, England; Los Angeles, Calif.; New York, N.Y. (Box 403)
    - Palm Beach, Fla.; Singapore; Washington, D.C.; Wichita, Kans. (Box 403)
  - 1987 (Box 403)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 403)
    - Worcester, Mass. (Box 403)
  - 1988 (Box 403)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 403, Box 404)
    - Cambridge, England (Box 404)
    - Hong Kong; Lisbon, Portugal (Box 404)
    - New York, N.Y.; Orlando, Fla. (Box 404)
    - San Francisco, Calif. (Box 404)
  - 1989 (Box 404)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 404)
    - San Juan, Puerto Rico (Box 404)
  - 1990 (Box 405)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 405)
    - Gstaad, Switzerland, Yehudi Menuhin concert hall (Box 405)
    - Los Angeles, Calif.; Nagoya, Japan (Box 405)
  - 1990-1994, Lisbon, Portugal (Box 405)
  - 1991 (Box 405)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 405)
    - Queens, N.Y. (Box 405)
    - San Francisco, Calif. (Box 406)
    - Wolfsburg, Germany (Box 406)
  - 1992 (Box 406)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 406)
    - Hong Kong (Box 406)
    - Toronto, Canada (Box 406)
    - Vienna, Austria (Box 406)
  - 1992-1993, Beijing, China, Olympics 2000, (2 folders) (Box 406)
  - 1993 (Box 406)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 406)
    - Nan Sha City, China (Box 407)
  - 1994 (Box 407)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 407)
    - Berlin, Germany; Leipzig, Germany (Box 407)
    - Neuss, Germany, (3 folders) (Box 407)
    - Rhine region, Germany (Box 408)
  - 1995 (Box 408)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 408)
    - Hong Kong (Box 408)
  - 1995-1996 (Box 408)
    - Lisbon, Portugal (Box 408)
    - Paris and Reims, France, Champagne Taittinger bottle (Box 408)
  - 1996 (Box 408)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 408)
    - L'Oréal perfume bottle (Box 409)
  - 1997 (Box 409)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 409)
    - Beijing, China, (2 folders) (Box 409)
  - 1997-1998, Beijing, China; Singapore (Box 409)
  - 1998 (Box 409)
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 409)
    - Vienna, Austria See also Digital Files, mss83787_123_044; mss83787_123_045 mss83787_123_046; mss83787_123_047; mss83787_123_048; mss83787_123_049, (4 folders) (Box 410)
    - Xiamen, China (Box 410)
  - 1999 (Box 410)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 410)
    - Amsterdam, Netherlands; Shenzhen, China (Box 410)
  - 2000 (Box 410)
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 410, Box 411)
    - Beijing, China; Berlin, Germany (Box 411)
    - Chengdu, China (Box 411)
  - 2000-2001, Beijing, China, U.S. Embassy (Box 411)
  - 2001 (Box 411)
    - Miscellaneous See also Container OV 10, 2001, miscellaneous (Box 411)
    - Beijing, China, Fragrant Hill Hotel restoration (Box 411)
    - Jinan, China; Shanghai, China (Box 411)
    - Shanghai, China; Tokyo, Japan (Box 411)
    - Valencia, Spain (Box 411)
  - 2002 (Box 411)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 411)
    - Leipzig, Germany (Box 412)
    - Lisbon, Portugal, (2 folders) (Box 412)
  - 2003 (Box 412)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 412)
    - Dubayy, United Arab Emirates (Box 412)
    - Manama, Bahrain; Millerton, N.Y. (Box 412)
    - Suzhou, China (Box 412)
  - 2004 (Box 413)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 413)
    - Beijing, China; Hagen, Germany; Jakarta, Indonesia; Mumbai, India (Box 413)
    - Shanghai, China; Singapore (Box 413)
  - 2005, miscellaneous (Box 413)
  - 2006, miscellaneous (Box 413)
  - 2007, miscellaneous (Box 413)
  - 2007-2008, Shanghai, China (Box 413)
  - 2008, miscellaneous (Box 413)
  - 2009 (Box 413)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 413)
    - Guadalajara, Mexico (Box 413)
  - 2010 (Box 413)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 413)
    - Suzhou, China; Taipei, Taiwan (Box 413)
  - 2011, miscellaneous (Box 413)
  - 2012, miscellaneous (Box 413)
- Publicity File, 1946-2012 (Box 414-443)